    'âš   BharatPay Pro â€” Already Running',
    'BharatPay Pro is already open on this machine.\n\n' +
    'Only one session is allowed at a time.\n\n' +
    'Please switch to the existing window.\n' +
    'If the app is unresponsive, close it from the Windows Taskbar and try again.'
  );
  app.quit();
} else {
  // If a second instance attempts while we are the primary, focus our window (only in prod).
  app.on('second-instance', () => {
    if (mainWindow && !isDev) {
      if (mainWindow.isMinimized()) mainWindow.restore();
      mainWindow.focus();
    }
  });
